[
    { "question" : "zijn", "answer" : "to be", "pronunciation" : "/zɛi̯n/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "hebben", "answer" : "to have", "pronunciation" : "/ˈɦaːbə(n)/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "kunnen", "answer" : "to be able to", "pronunciation" : "/ˈkʏnə(n)/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "willen", "answer" : "to want", "pronunciation" : "/ˈwɪlə(n)/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "moeten", "answer" : "must", "pronunciation" : "/ˈmuːstə(n)/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "mogen", "answer" : "may", "pronunciation" : "/ˈmoːɣə(n)/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "gaan", "answer" : "to go", "pronunciation" : "/ɣaːn/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "doen", "answer" : "to do", "pronunciation" : "/du(n)/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "zeggen", "answer" : "to say", "pronunciation" : "/ˈzɛɣə(n)/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "komen", "answer" : "to come", "pronunciation" : "/ˈkoːmə(n)/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "denken", "answer" : "to think", "pronunciation" : "/ˈdɛŋkə(n)/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "vinden", "answer" : "to find", "pronunciation" : "/ˈvɪndə(n)/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "zien", "answer" : "to see", "pronunciation" : "/ziːn/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "laten", "answer" : "to let", "pronunciation" : "/ˈlaːtə(n)/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "geven", "answer" : "to give", "pronunciation" : "/ˈɣeːvə(n)/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "spreken", "answer" : "to speak", "pronunciation" : "/ˈspreːkə(n)/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "nemen", "answer" : "to take", "pronunciation" : "/ˈneːmə(n)/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "staan", "answer" : "to stand", "pronunciation" : "/staːn/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "krijgen", "answer" : "to get", "pronunciation" : "/ˈkrɛi̯ɣə(n)/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "horen", "answer" : "to hear", "pronunciation" : "/ˈɦoːrə(n)/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "werken", "answer" : "to work", "pronunciation" : "/ˈʋɛrkə(n)/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "leven", "answer" : "to live", "pronunciation" : "/ˈleːvə(n)/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "maken", "answer" : "to make", "pronunciation" : "/ˈmaːkə(n)/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "laten", "answer" : "to leave", "pronunciation" : "/ˈlaːtə(n)/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "voelen", "answer" : "to feel", "pronunciation" : "/ˈvuːlə(n)/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "komen", "answer" : "to become", "pronunciation" : "/ˈkoːmə(n)/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "vinden", "answer" : "to think", "pronunciation" : "/ˈvɪndə(n)/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "blijven", "answer" : "to stay", "pronunciation" : "/ˈblɛi̯və(n)/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "krijgen", "answer" : "to be given", "pronunciation" : "/ˈkrɛi̯ɣə(n)/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "kunnen", "answer" : "to be possible", "pronunciation" : "/ˈkʏnə(n)/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "zetten", "answer" : "to put", "pronunciation" : "/ˈzɛtə(n)/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "betekenen", "answer" : "to mean", "pronunciation" : "/ˈbeːtəkənə(n)/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "volgen", "answer" : "to follow", "pronunciation" : "/ˈvɔlɣə(n)/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "praten", "answer" : "to talk", "pronunciation" : "/ˈpraːtə(n)/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "vragen", "answer" : "to ask", "pronunciation" : "/ˈfraːɣə(n)/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "brengen", "answer" : "to bring", "pronunciation" : "/ˈbrɛŋə(n)/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "kiezen", "answer" : "to choose", "pronunciation" : "/ˈkiːzə(n)/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "schrijven", "answer" : "to write", "pronunciation" : "/ˈsxrɛi̯və(n)/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "kopen", "answer" : "to buy", "pronunciation" : "/ˈkoːpə(n)/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "huis", "answer" : "house", "pronunciation" : "/hœys/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "tijd", "answer" : "time", "pronunciation" : "/tɛit/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "man", "answer" : "man", "pronunciation" : "/mɑn/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "vrouw", "answer" : "woman", "pronunciation" : "/vrɑu/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "kind", "answer" : "child", "pronunciation" : "/kɪnt/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "ding", "answer" : "thing", "pronunciation" : "/dɪŋ/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "leven", "answer" : "life", "pronunciation" : "/leːvə(n)/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "werk", "answer" : "work", "pronunciation" : "/wɛrk/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "geld", "answer" : "money", "pronunciation" : "/ɣɛlt/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "stad", "answer" : "city", "pronunciation" : "/stɑt/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "land", "answer" : "country", "pronunciation" : "/lɑnt/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "mens", "answer" : "human", "pronunciation" : "/mɛns/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "probleem", "answer" : "problem", "pronunciation" : "/prɔbleːm/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "vraag", "answer" : "question", "pronunciation" : "/vraːɣ/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "antwoord", "answer" : "answer", "pronunciation" : "/ˈɑntʋoːrt/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "oorlog", "answer" : "war", "pronunciation" : "/oːrlɑx/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "vrede", "answer" : "peace", "pronunciation" : "/vreːdə/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "vriend", "answer" : "friend", "pronunciation" : "/vrint/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "familie", "answer" : "family", "pronunciation" : "/fɑˈmi.li/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "moeder", "answer" : "mother", "pronunciation" : "/ˈmu.dər/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "vader", "answer" : "father", "pronunciation" : "/ˈva.dər/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "dochter", "answer" : "daughter", "pronunciation" : "/ˈdɔx.tər/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "zoon", "answer" : "son", "pronunciation" : "/zoːn/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "lichaam", "answer" : "body", "pronunciation" : "/ˈli.xaːm/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "hart", "answer" : "heart", "pronunciation" : "/hɑrt/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "hoofd", "answer" : "head", "pronunciation" : "/hoːft/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "hand", "answer" : "hand", "pronunciation" : "/hɑnt/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "voet", "answer" : "foot", "pronunciation" : "/voːt/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "mond", "answer" : "mouth", "pronunciation" : "/mɔnt/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "oog", "answer" : "eye", "pronunciation" : "/oːx/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "neus", "answer" : "nose", "pronunciation" : "/nøːs/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "oor", "answer" : "ear", "pronunciation" : "/oːr/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "eten", "answer" : "food", "pronunciation" : "/ˈeːtən/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "water", "answer" : "water", "pronunciation" : "/ˈʋaːtər/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "wijn", "answer" : "wine", "pronunciation" : "/ʋɛin/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "bier", "answer" : "beer", "pronunciation" : "/biːr/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "koffie", "answer" : "coffee", "pronunciation" : "/ˈkɔ.fi/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "thee", "answer" : "tea", "pronunciation" : "/teː/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "melk", "answer" : "milk", "pronunciation" : "/mɛlk/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "brood", "answer" : "bread", "pronunciation" : "/broːt/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "kaas", "answer" : "cheese", "pronunciation" : "/kaːs/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "vlees", "answer" : "meat", "pronunciation" : "/vleːs/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "vis", "answer" : "fish", "pronunciation" : "/vɪs/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "groente", "answer" : "vegetables", "pronunciation" : "/ˈɣru.nə(n)tə/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "fruit", "answer" : "fruit", "pronunciation" : "/frœy̯t/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "auto", "answer" : "car", "pronunciation" : "/ˈɔtoː/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "fiets", "answer" : "bicycle", "pronunciation" : "/fits/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "trein", "answer" : "train", "pronunciation" : "/trɛin/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "bus", "answer" : "bus", "pronunciation" : "/bɵs/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "vliegtuig", "answer" : "airplane", "pronunciation" : "/ˈvlit.ˌtœy̯χ/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "mooi", "answer" : "beautiful", "pronunciation" : "/moːi/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "goed", "answer" : "good", "pronunciation" : "/ɣut/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "groot", "answer" : "big", "pronunciation" : "/ɣroːt/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "klein", "answer" : "small", "pronunciation" : "/klɛi̯n/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "nieuw", "answer" : "new", "pronunciation" : "/niu/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "oud", "answer" : "old", "pronunciation" : "/ɑu̯t/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "jong", "answer" : "young", "pronunciation" : "/jɔŋ/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "lang", "answer" : "long", "pronunciation" : "/lɑŋ/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "kort", "answer" : "short", "pronunciation" : "/kɔrt/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "zwaar", "answer" : "heavy", "pronunciation" : "/zwaːr/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "licht", "answer" : "light", "pronunciation" : "/lɪxt/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "makkelijk", "answer" : "easy", "pronunciation" : "/mɑkəlik/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "moeilijk", "answer" : "difficult", "pronunciation" : "/muilək/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "snel", "answer" : "fast", "pronunciation" : "/snel/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "traag", "answer" : "slow", "pronunciation" : "/traːx/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "lekker", "answer" : "delicious", "pronunciation" : "/lɛkər/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "slecht", "answer" : "bad", "pronunciation" : "/slɛxt/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "duur", "answer" : "expensive", "pronunciation" : "/dyːr/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "goedkoop", "answer" : "cheap", "pronunciation" : "/ɣutkoːp/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "simpel", "answer" : "simple", "pronunciation" : "/sɪmpəl/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "ingewikkeld", "answer" : "complicated", "pronunciation" : "/ɪŋəˈʋɪkəlt/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "vrolijk", "answer" : "cheerful", "pronunciation" : "/vroːlək/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "triest", "answer" : "sad", "pronunciation" : "/trist/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "donker", "answer" : "dark", "pronunciation" : "/dɔŋkər/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "luid", "answer" : "loud", "pronunciation" : "/lœyt/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "stil", "answer" : "quiet", "pronunciation" : "/stɪl/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "nat", "answer" : "wet", "pronunciation" : "/nɑt/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "droog", "answer" : "dry", "pronunciation" : "/droːx/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "gezellig", "answer" : "cozy", "pronunciation" : "/ɣəˈzɛləx/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "saai", "answer" : "boring", "pronunciation" : "/saːi̯/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "interessant", "answer" : "interesting", "pronunciation" : "/ɪntərɛˈsɑnt/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "belangrijk", "answer" : "important", "pronunciation" : "/bɛˈlɑŋrəik/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "beroemd", "answer" : "famous", "pronunciation" : "/bəˈruːmd/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "onbekend", "answer" : "unknown", "pronunciation" : "/ɔnbəˈkɛnt/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "gezond", "answer" : "healthy", "pronunciation" : "/ɣəˈzɔnt/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "ziek", "answer" : "sick", "pronunciation" : "/ziːk/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "bezorgd", "answer" : "worried", "pronunciation" : "/bəˈzɔrx/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "gelukkig", "answer" : "happy", "pronunciation" : "/ɣəˈlɵkəx/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "ongelukkig", "answer" : "unhappy", "pronunciation" : "/ɔŋəˈlɵkəx/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "trots", "answer" : "proud", "pronunciation" : "/trots/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "beschaamd", "answer" : "ashamed", "pronunciation" : "/bəˈsxaːmd/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "verlegen", "answer" : "shy", "pronunciation" : "/vərˈleːɣən/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "moedig", "answer" : "brave", "pronunciation" : "/muːdəx/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "bang", "answer" : "afraid", "pronunciation" : "/bɑŋ/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "nieuwsgierig", "answer" : "curious", "pronunciation" : "/niu̯sɣiˈryx/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "vriendelijk", "answer" : "friendly", "pronunciation" : "/vriənˈdələk/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "heel", "answer" : "very", "pronunciation" : "/ɦeːl/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "daarom", "answer" : "therefore", "pronunciation" : "/daːˈrɔm/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "nogal", "answer" : "rather", "pronunciation" : "/ˈnoːɣɑl/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "wel", "answer" : "well", "pronunciation" : "/ʋɛl/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "misschien", "answer" : "perhaps", "pronunciation" : "/ˈmɪs.xin/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "soms", "answer" : "sometimes", "pronunciation" : "/sɔms/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "hier", "answer" : "here", "pronunciation" : "/ˈɦiːr/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "zo", "answer" : "so", "pronunciation" : "/zoː/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "echt", "answer" : "really", "pronunciation" : "/ɛxt/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "altijd", "answer" : "always", "pronunciation" : "/ˈɑl.tɛit/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "weer", "answer" : "again", "pronunciation" : "/ʋeːr/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "ook", "answer" : "also", "pronunciation" : "/oːk/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "nog", "answer" : "still", "pronunciation" : "/nɔx/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "al", "answer" : "already", "pronunciation" : "/ɑl/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "bijna", "answer" : "almost", "pronunciation" : "/ˈbɛi.na/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "net", "answer" : "just", "pronunciation" : "/nɛt/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "dan", "answer" : "then", "pronunciation" : "/dɑn/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "even", "answer" : "briefly", "pronunciation" : "/ˈeː.vən/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "heel veel", "answer" : "very much", "pronunciation" : "/ɦeːl veːl/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "weinig", "answer" : "little", "pronunciation" : "/ˈwɛi.nɪx/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "vandaag", "answer" : "today", "pronunciation" : "/ˈvɑn.daːx/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "gisteren", "answer" : "yesterday", "pronunciation" : "/ˈɣɪs.tər.ə(n)/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "morgen", "answer" : "tomorrow", "pronunciation" : "/ˈmɔr.ɣə(n)/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "ooit", "answer" : "ever", "pronunciation" : "/oːt/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "alweer", "answer" : "already again", "pronunciation" : "/ˈɑl.ʋeːr/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "te", "answer" : "too", "pronunciation" : "/tə/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "erg", "answer" : "very", "pronunciation" : "/ɛrx/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "zeker", "answer" : "sure", "pronunciation" : "/ˈzeː.kər/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "nauwelijks", "answer" : "hardly", "pronunciation" : "/ˈnʌu̯.ʋə.ˌlɛi̯ks/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "graag", "answer" : "gladly", "pronunciation" : "/ɣraːx/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "zoveel", "answer" : "so much", "pronunciation" : "/ˈzoː.veːl/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "eindelijk", "answer" : "finally", "pronunciation" : "/ˈɛin.də.lək/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "liever", "answer" : "rather", "pronunciation" : "/ˈliː.vər/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "best", "answer" : "best", "pronunciation" : "/bɛst/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "bijvoorbeeld", "answer" : "for example", "pronunciation" : "/ˈbɛi̯.vʊr.beːlt/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "alsnog", "answer" : "still", "pronunciation" : "/ˈɑl.snɔx/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "vanavond", "answer" : "this evening", "pronunciation" : "/ˈvɑn.ɑvɔnt/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "zó", "answer" : "like this", "pronunciation" : "/zoː/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "opnieuw", "answer" : "again", "pronunciation" : "/ˈɔp.niːu̯/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "helaas", "answer" : "unfortunately", "pronunciation" : "/heː.ˈlaːs/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "helemaal", "answer" : "completely", "pronunciation" : "/ɦeː.lə.ˈmal/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "en", "answer" : "and", "pronunciation" : "/ɛn/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "of", "answer" : "or", "pronunciation" : "/ɔf/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "maar", "answer" : "but", "pronunciation" : "/maːr/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "want", "answer" : "because", "pronunciation" : "/vɔnt/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "toch", "answer" : "still/yet", "pronunciation" : "/tɔx/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "omdat", "answer" : "because", "pronunciation" : "/ɔmˈsɑt/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "dus", "answer" : "so/therefore", "pronunciation" : "/dʏs/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "als", "answer" : "if", "pronunciation" : "/ɑls/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "hoewel", "answer" : "although", "pronunciation" : "/huˈʋɛl/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "terwijl", "answer" : "while", "pronunciation" : "/tɛrˈʋɛil/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "zodat", "answer" : "so that", "pronunciation" : "/zoˈdɑt/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "sinds", "answer" : "since", "pronunciation" : "/sɪnts/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "tot", "answer" : "until", "pronunciation" : "/tɔt/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "toen", "answer" : "then", "pronunciation" : "/tun/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "ofwel", "answer" : "or rather", "pronunciation" : "/ɔfˈʋɛl/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "echter", "answer" : "however", "pronunciation" : "/ɛxtər/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "namelijk", "answer" : "namely", "pronunciation" : "/ˈnaːmələk/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "daarom", "answer" : "therefore", "pronunciation" : "/ˈdaːrɔm/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "anders", "answer" : "otherwise", "pronunciation" : "/ˈɑndərs/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "behalve", "answer" : "except for", "pronunciation" : "/bəˈɦɑlvə/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "evenals", "answer" : "as well as", "pronunciation" : "/ˈeːvənɑls/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "beide", "answer" : "both", "pronunciation" : "/ˈbɛidə/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "noch", "answer" : "neither/nor", "pronunciation" : "/nɔx/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "voor", "answer" : "for/before", "pronunciation" : "/voːr/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "nadat", "answer" : "after", "pronunciation" : "/ˈnaːdɑt/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "omdat", "answer" : "because", "pronunciation" : "/ɔmˈsɑt/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "al", "answer" : "already", "pronunciation" : "/ɑl/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "hoewel", "answer" : "although", "pronunciation" : "/huˈʋɛl/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "aangezien", "answer" : "since/because", "pronunciation" : "/ˈaːŋəzɛin/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "daar", "answer" : "there", "pronunciation" : "/daːr/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "verder", "answer" : "furthermore", "pronunciation" : "/ˈvɛrdər/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "ook al", "answer" : "even though", "pronunciation" : "/oːk ɑl/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "zowel als", "answer" : "as well as", "pronunciation" : "/ˈzoːwɛl ɑls/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "tevens", "answer" : "also", "pronunciation" : "/ˈtevəns/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "zeker", "answer" : "certainly", "pronunciation" : "/ˈzeːkər/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "omdat", "answer" : "because", "pronunciation" : "/ɔmˈsɑt/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "noch", "answer" : "neither/nor", "pronunciation" : "/nɔx/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "behalve", "answer" : "except for", "pronunciation" : "/bəˈɦɑlvə/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "toen", "answer" : "then", "pronunciation" : "/tun/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "toch", "answer" : "still/yet", "pronunciation" : "/tɔx/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "terwijl", "answer" : "while", "pronunciation" : "/tɛrˈʋɛil/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "zodra", "answer" : "as soon as", "pronunciation" : "/ˈzoːdrɑ/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "weliswaar", "answer" : "admittedly", "pronunciation" : "/ˈʋɛlisˌʋaːr/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "zoals", "answer" : "such as", "pronunciation" : "/zoˈalsə/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" }
]